Pamod Gurusinghe

Associate QA Engineer

Experienced professional Quality Assurance Engineer with 2 years of experience in software quality assurance and manual testing. Currently focused on enhancing skills in test automation to optimize testing processes and drive product quality. Seeking an Opportunity to Leverage Skills and Drive Excellence in Quality Assurance.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Jan 2022 - Jan 2023

Associate QA Engineer

Agrithmics (Pvt) Ltd I 90 Gothami Rd, Colombo.

- Involved in Requirement analysis, Test Case creation, Defect Tracking, and Test Case execution.
- Performed manual testing on the ERP web application.
- Conducted pre-release testing for functional validation before every release and deployment.
- Maintained and updated test documentation.
- Tracked bugs using the bug tracking system (Azure DevOps).
- led 2 applications and worked closely with the development team and was responsible for the complete STLC.

Jun 2020 - May 2021

Intern QA Engineer

Virtusa Pvt. Ltd I 752 Dr Danister De Silva Mawatha, Colombo.

- Analyzed software requirements, developed test documentation including test cases, and checklists,
- Executed and maintained test cases and test suites.
- Reported detailed bug reports and followed them through the whole life cycle, working with ERA.
- Maintained and updated test documentation between releases.
- Worked closely with the development team, being one of the two QA engineers.

EDUCATION

• 2018 - 2022

B.SC. (HONS) INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY SPECIALIZING IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

SRI LANKA INSTITUTE OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY (SLIIT)

• 2017

G.C.E ADVANCED LEVEL - 3 C (COMMERCE STREAM)
KULARATHNA COLLEGE - AMBALANGODA

• 2014

G.C.E ORDINARY LEVEL

KULARATHNA COLLEGE - AMBALANGODA

CONTACTS

070 305 4972

pamodgurusinghe@gmail.com

in pamod-gurusinghe

No 289/A, Ella Road,Elpitiya.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- SQL
- Java
- Postman
- MS Office
- Azure DevOps

SOFT SKILLS

- Time Management
- Team Work
- Adaptability
- Attention to detail
- Self-Starter
- Lifelong Learner

LANGUAGE

- Sinhala
- English